Carly, get in here, right now.
Have a seat.
So, I understand you put
some fliers up
all over the school?
Yes, I did.
Why would you Photodoc my head
onto the body of a rhinoceros?
Well, I...
Rhinoceros? Oh, no, no, no.
She made you a hippopotamus.
No, no.
She's a rhinoceros.
A hippo has fatter thighs
and a wider snout.
What does it matter?
I think we should call
her father in to discuss this.
Um, my dad's stationed
in Europe right now.
He's in the military.
Well, there must be
some adult in charge of her.
My older brother, Spencer.
Oh, yes, the artist.
He's a great artist.
Look, we don't need to call
her brother in about this.
I'm sure that you can come up
with a suitable punishment.
Fine.
You know, Carly, I am in charge
of the talent show this year.
Yeah, you're holding
auditions on Saturday.
No, you are.
Huh?!
I will be enjoying my Saturday
while you videotape
the auditions for me.
No! I'm going to see
Cuddlefish play live
at the Hawthorne on Saturday!
Not anymore.
Aw, come on!
It's what you get for
turning me into a hippopotamus.
Rhinoceros.
Get out!
Right.
In five, four, three, two...
♪
♪ I know, you see ♪
♪ Somehow the world
will change for me ♪
♪ And be so wonderful ♪
♪
♪ Live life, breathe air ♪
♪ I know somehow
we're gonna get there ♪
♪ And feel so wonderful ♪
♪ It's all for real ♪
♪ I'm telling you
just how I feel ♪
♪ So wake up the members
of my nation ♪
♪ It's your time to be ♪
♪ There's no chance
unless you take one ♪
♪ And the time to see
the brighter side ♪
♪ Of every situation ♪
♪ Some things are meant to be
so give me your best ♪
♪ And leave the rest to me ♪
♪ Leave it all to me,
leave it all to me ♪
♪ Just leave it all to me ♪
♪
Ah! Let me go!
Say you're sorry.
I'm sorry!
And what are you sorry for?
For saying you're aggressive!
And what am I, again?
Pretty and sweet!
Thank you! Now the next time...
Ow! Hair, hair, hair.
Hi!
Did you get in trouble?
Of course I got in trouble!
Teachers tend to get upset
when you put their heads
on the bodies of big,
fat animals!
I can't believe
I let you talk me
into taking the blame for you!
You had to. I've already been
suspended once this semester.
If I'd gotten busted,
they'd have expelled me.
Well, here's an idea.
What?
Stop doing bad things!
Okay. Chillax.
I will not chillax!
And get excited,
'cause you and I get to spend
our entire Saturday here
videotaping kids' auditions
for the talent show.
Whatev.
You know, anybody but me would
punch you right in the head.
Which is why you are
my best friend.
Good to know.
Now, why are you mine?
Because I'm a lovable person.
♪
You dropped this!
Um, thanks, but you really...
I was gonna walk you
home from school
but I couldn't find ya. Hey!
Freddie, were you
looking out your peephole
waiting for me to come home?
No!
Freddie.
Yes.
I thought we talked about this.
We can be buds, but you gotta
get over this crush thing.
I am over it. Seriously.
I'm in love with you.
You just wanna be friends.
And I'm totally cool
living with that constant pain.
Oh, god.
I'm home.
Hey, kiddo! Up here.
Just taking some pics
of my robot sculpture.
Smile! Yeah.
You know, for most
eighth grade girls,
if they came home and found
their 26-year-old brother
dangling upside down
from the ceiling
over a giant robot
made out of soda bottles,
it'd be weird.
You're saying I'm abnormal.
Do I need to say it?
Come down from there
before you hurt yourself.
No worries.
I got my leg wrapped
around this pipe... Ah!
Please help me stand up.
Are you all right?
Yea... Nope.
I dislocated my shoulder again.
One sec.
Yeah, that fixed her.
Good.
So listen, I need a favor.
Shoot.
I have to tape
a bunch of auditions
at school on Saturday.
Fun.
Yeah, not really.
Anyway, would you let me
borrow your video camera?
I would.
Awesome.
Though I can't.
Why not?
I made it into a squirrel.
♪
I told you the front doors
would be locked.
You gotta go around to the blue
doors in the back of the...
Oh, my God.
What do you think
of my equipment?
I just asked to borrow
your video camera.
What is all this?
Well, that's a three-chip,
high-def camcorder
with a hyper-cardioid
condenser microphone.
Mounted on a carbon fiber tripod
with a low-drag fluid head.
I also brought you
juice and a bagel.
Hey, you invited the doof.
Sam.
Aw, man! I didn't know
that was gonna be here.
She. I'm a she, Freddie,
as in "girl."
Just keep your hands
off my AV equipment.
You mean I can't play
with the white balance
on your super-dee duper-dee
camcorder?
Ah, sure! Everybody jokes
about the white balance
'til the skin tones
go magenta...
Carly will never love you.
That's it!
I'm taking my stuff
and I'm going home!
Please stay.
Okay.
Okay, Jeb,
you ready to audition?
Yeah. I will be performing
a scene from a French play
called...
Okay.
We don't know what
that means, but knock us out.
Rolling?
Uh... rolling.
But... but
where did she go?
I don't know.
But when will she be back?
I don't know!
Well, where can I find her?
I tell you, I do not know!
Okay!
Nice job!
What'd you think?
I don't know!
You don't know?!
I tell you, I do not know!
But you must know!
How can I know
when I do not know?
I don't know.
♪
I will play the trumpet.
Great.
Nice.
While hopping
on this pogo stick.
♪
That's what I'm talking about!
Great job!
You go, girl! Yeah.
Pogo-tastic!
That's awesome!
Jump and blow!
So the doc says,
"Why'd you wait so long
to bring her in?"
So I say, "I liked the eggs."
That's awesome.
Thanks.
Not that funny.
No, no, not at all.
But forget that.
Can we please discuss
the boy's hair and glasses?
He looks like Miss Briggs.
Yeah, except he doesn't have
Miss Briggs' crazy pointy boobs.
I know!
What is up with those?
It's like she stuffs
waffle cones in her bra.
Totally! She could
poke an eye out
with one of those things.
Okay, okay,
we better keep going.
We've still got 11 more
kids to see.
No.
Eleven?
Calm down.
They can't get worse.
And I was wrong.
♪
Sam.
Wake up!
What time is it?
Late. What time is your mom
coming to pick you up?
She's not. I told her you
invited me to spend the night.
I didn't invite you
to spend the night.
Well, you should
'cause I'm not leaving.
What you doing?
Checking to make sure Freddie
put the auditions online.
I told Miss Briggs
we'd upload 'em
on SplashFace tonight so she
could watch 'em in the morning.
I kind of hate Miss Briggs.
Remember when
she called me a demon?
No!
Oh, Yeah.
When I put that
raw chicken in her purse...
Shut up and come look at this!
What? Freddie didn't
upload the auditions?
No! He uploaded us!
What?
Look!
It's like she stuffs
waffle cones in her bra.
That's you and me!
Sure is!
He wasn't supposed to film us!
We were being all goofy
and acting like idiots all day!
Oh, my God.
We made fun of Miss Briggs
and her crazy pointy boobs!
Whoa, if she sees that...
Anyone can see it!
It's on SplashFace!
Okay, okay, chillax.
Look, see the view count?
Only 27 people
have clicked on it.
Oh. Okay, good.
Sam?
Yeah.
That's 27,000!
♪
Quit it, Sam!
Let go of my foot!
Too much friction! Let go!
What is the matter with you?!
Why'd you film us
at the auditions today?
Oh. 'Cause you guys
were being funny.
Well, you shouldn't have
put us online
without our permission!
I didn't!
I edited you guys out
before I uploaded the auditions.
No, you did
the opposite of that!
What? There's no way I...
Uh-oh.
Yeah.
Just take us off the site!
Okay, okay!
Just give me a sec.
Oh, this is so not good.
Anyone, anyone in the world
can just click and see
everything we did
and said today.
It's so embarrassing.
And if Miss Briggs...
Don't even talk about it.
If she...
Ha! Got it.
See? It says,
"At your request,
this video will be removed."
Good!
Finally.
Tomorrow morning.
Ugh, great.
Aw, man!
Do you know how many
more thousands
can view it by then?
Alright!
Look, before you get
all freaked out,
SplashFace has message boards.
So?
So, let's see
what people are saying
about the video.
Um, okay, here's one.
"Carly, you and your
friend Sam crack me up.
Funny stuff."
Great, so one kid...
Wait.
SlackerBoy314 writes,
"Carly and Sam,
you chicks are hilarious.
When's your next show?"
And this kid says,
"You guys are way better
than most of the puke
here on SplashFace."
Wow. They love us.
Yeah! More than puke.
♪
Where's Miss Briggs?
What if she saw it?
Video was off
by yesterday morning.
What if she saw it
before it was off?
It was Sunday.
She was probably in church.
What church would let
Miss Briggs in the door?
Hello, Carly. Samantha.
Howdy.
Morning, Miss Briggs.
Um, we had some trouble
putting the video online,
so here's a DVD of every kid
who auditioned on Saturday.
Thank you.
Sure.
I'll try not to poke a hole
in this with my pointy bosoms.
She saw the video.
We're so sorry.
Miss Briggs?
What?
I typed up a list of the kids
we think should be
in the talent show.
Snorting milk?
Pogo stick hopping?
These aren't talents.
They were the most fun to watch.
Goodbye.
Wait, so you're not gonna
let any of the kids
we picked be in the show?
That's right. Girls.
No one enjoys that!
♪
I am so mad!
Me, too.
I need some ham.
Seriously,
Miss Briggs is the worst!
You don't gotta convince me.
I hated her even after
she got that brown lump
removed from her nose.
I'll tell you something.
She is what's wrong
with the world.
Who's what's wrong
with the world?
Miss Briggs.
Oh.
Well, hey, at least she got
that brown lump
taken off of her nose.
I just hate it
when adults like her
get to control what kids
can do and see.
It ticks me off.
Why do they put a bone
right in the middle of a ham?
Hey, remember all that stuff
those kids wrote about us
on the message boards?
Yeah.
Things like, "You guys
should upload more videos,"
and, "When's your next show?"
And, "We want more."
Let's give 'em more.
More?
Okay, what are we
talking about here?
Doing a web show,
online, every week.
Why?
'Cause it can be
whatever we want it to be,
no adults to say,
"You can do this.
You can't do that."
We can do whatever we want,
say whatever we want.
Would it mean I have to do,
like, work and stuff?
Well, if you're gonna do it,
you gotta prepare for it.
Eh, then make it your show.
You do the work,
I'll just show up
and be your amusing little
sidekick.
Wait, what's the show
gonna be about?
Anything.
Something different every week.
But for the first show,
kids with bizarro talents.
Ah, clever.
Miss Briggs says,
"No, no, no."
We say, "Yeah, yeah, yeah."
Hey, why don't you guys
call your show "iCarly."
You know, "I," Internet,
"Carly," you.
I like it.
ICarly's cool.
And um, you're gonna need
a technical producer, right?
To set up the lights, audio,
work the camera...
Aw, he wants to be our geek.
You got a big mouth, lady!
Hey! Look what someone
just left in the dumpster.
Isn't she amazing?!
Hey, can we use the third
floor as kind of a TV studio?
Well, I don't know...
Thanks!
You rock.
Later!
Wait, I didn't say...
Why do you... Okay, later!
♪
52 seconds!
Sam, come on!
Sorry, I had to pee!
You always have to pee.
Well, it's either that
or I explode.
45 seconds!
We're on our way up!
You know what to do?
Yes.
We sit together;
me on the left,
you on the right.
Camera opens on the sign,
pans down to me.
We chat with all the kids
with weird talents.
You got it?
I'm down.
20 seconds.
Here we go.
I look good?
Perfect. Me?
Uh, well, you got
something in your teeth.
What?! Get it out!
Five! Four!
Three! Two, and...
Hey, there, people of Earth.
I'm Carly Shay,
and this is our very first
webcast
of a little show we call iCarly.
She's Carly.
She's Sam.
Sam I am.
Carly, Sam.
I think they're clear.
Demonstrate the thing.
Oh, yeah! With this item,
provided by our dorky friend,
Freddie...
That's disrespectful!
We can do this...
and this.
And this...
♪
Okay.
Tonight, we're gonna show you
some kids
with super insane talents.
♪ Freak show! ♪
Stop it.
Okay, this first kid
we're gonna show you
can take a glass of milk...
This is so deliciously gross.
Snort the milk up into his nose.
It's the best thing ever.
And make the milk
squirt out of his eyes.
I wanna marry this boy!
Let's bring him out.
Simon Kendall!
You're up, dude!
Okay, Simon, you ready
to blow people away
with your freakish talent?
Do it!
Let's go.
Drum roll.
Okay, this is insane!
Tell the people your name.
Brennan Yubberly.
Yeah, Yubberly!
Okay, any word you say,
Brennan can say backwards
perfectly.
He's a backwards talker.
Check this out.
Ointment.
Tnenmtnio.
Yes! Okay, uh,
slippery watermelon.
Yreppils nolemretaw.
Do you hear this?
We love this boy!
Okay, okay! Say,
"I must be from planet Jupiter
"because there's no other way
I could be saying all this
backwards!"
I tsum eb morf tenalp retipuJ
esuaceb s'ereht on rehto yaw
I dluoc eb gniyas lla siht
sdrawkcab.
Did you hear that?
Insanity!
Ytinasni!
That's enough, Brennan.
Yeah! Great job!
Wonderful!
Well, looking at that goat
made me hungry!
Well, you can eat soon,
'cause the very first webcast
of iCarly is almost over.
No, no, don't be sad.
We still got one more kid
with a weird talent. But first...
Here's some stuff
you need to know.
If you liked our show,
tell your friends.
Your cousins, people you like.
People you hate.
All people of this planet.
That we're gonna be here,
live, online,
every week at iCarly.com.
In fact, next week,
Carly's gonna take
my tonsils out right here.
She's lying.
But how awesome would that be?
Oh! And if you wanna
send us a video...
Of you doing
or saying anything cool.
Telling a joke, eating a bug.
Just email the video clip to us.
Carly and me.
Me and Sam.
At iCarly.com
And if it's cool enough...
We'll show it right here
on iCarly.
Okay, our last freakishly
talented kid's name
is Taryn James,
and she's about to play us out.
With her trumpet.
But with a little extra twist.
Hit the button.
Get out here, Taryn!
♪ Will you look at that!
It seems impossible.
That is so cool!
I wish I could do that!
Come on, let's go!
Yeah!
Well, thanks for watching!
Tune in next time!
Oh, my gosh!
This is so much fun!
And we're clear!
Yes! We did it!
Oh, here it is!
How many?
37,000!
Why are we happy?
'Cause our very first
web show rocked!
And was watched by over
37,000 people!
Get out!
My baby sister's a web star!
Hey, we should have a party,
you know, to celebrate.
Yeah, that'd be so cool.
That'd be so tight!
Yes. Yes, we should.
But it shouldn't be
a normal, regular party.
Oh no.
It needs to be something
different,
something... wonderfully random.
Crazy hat party?
♪
Hey, cupcake.
There you are! Nice hat.
Back at ya.
Hi. Um, can we get
your autographs?
We love iCarly.
Your web show.
Um, sure.
No prob.
There you go.
Thanks.
Sure.
I love you, Carly!
Wow.
I just signed an autograph.
Get used to it.
ICarly's a great show.
You might get famous.
Yeah, I don't know
if I'm gonna like that.
Hey.
Saw your web show.
Pretty hot.
Um, thanks.
Yeah, thanks a lot.
So, you guys wanna dance?
Yes.
Cool, let's do it.
I'm gonna like it.
Hey! Hey, stop that!
Put her down!
She's not for you!
Get off! How pitiful!
Who invited you?!
♪
Woo!
Mmm.